Hello friends, welcome to this topic YouTube channel.
Friends, today we have
brought another wealth creator stock which
can give you a good fortune in the coming time. One share is definitely a share,
friends, it is the leader of our tractor.
Whatever I played in my channel, friends, it is a
fundamentally strong share and a
leader share of its sector which
can give you a great fortune. The
purpose of this channel of mine is that friends, even the
retail investor who does not know anything should at
least know after watching this video
that yes, this stock can do something, so he should
invest a little in it. So that is our
objective that we all together should
create a belt. So which is that city? So let
me take you to my screen.
Before that, friends, I
would request you to come to the channel for the first time and
subscribe to the channel and also
click the bell icon so that whenever I make a
video call, you
get a notification and you do not miss any wealth creator. So,
let me take you to the screen, so
see this on the screen, friends, you
can directly see who  This is the
Vice Chief of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company, this company
is related to General Insurance and this company
is friends, why am I talking about this right now that
you should always keep in mind that by clicking on any
market, share it and keep it in rest mode,
in rally,
we have to fold it, when it is in rest mode,
what we have to do is we should do it for a minute,
tie it in a knot and we should always do it,
but now we should start doing it for a minute, if we
do it here and press test, a horizontal
line is drawn, I rest it a little so that
you will not be able to see, this line is a
resistance line,
why, because this line was drawn
in the month of December, it gave a break but could
not subscribe to the flashlight,
what happened in the next month, you broke the low of the month of December and
came down again, so we can say that this
fabric Mukta, so after the fabric out,
what happened, it again came into correction mode, that is,
it is running in correction mode and
see, its lower, so low and here
I have drawn another horizontal line rock  So what will this be, the
support line? Now look, the
card that was put in this month, due to panic,
we saw so much Selina in the month, but this
line of ours will be of the line, support
means from 1000 to 1450,
a range of 1000 to 1450 is being formed, this is the entire
range, friends, AP Jain says, okay, just
like you do the same in mutual funds,
you should set up your own in your city, do
not put money in lump sum at once, you have to
put everything for a long time, in any of this, if
you feel that there is fundamentalism, then these
people, every zone is my support level,
you should put rice there, so what should I do,
what will be my strategy, you will work in this
area, in this
every month I will do one or two shares for a
minute in this entire zone, from 1000
to 1400 and it is not that this is any meaningful
option, decide it yourself,
like your salary comes on the 5th, you have to pay
and the 5th stays within this range,
buy one share, buy two shares,
so this is what I am telling you
friends, support  Resistance. Look at this. Now, it might
seem like it's very easy,
friends. Investing is very easy,
but what people have done is
complicated it. That's why
retail investors can't make money. What they do is they keep chasing
small stocks. Do
n't go after the pink shirt at all. What we have to do is fundamentally
catch this sector and keep adding to it.
This is also in correction mode right now,
and the market is almost at that time. Is the market in a rally?
But keep this area covered. The
correction that has happened, you have to type in
that video. You can watch it. A
simple correction will be important, which gets
activated well
when a correction happens. What do we do at that time?
We regulate it. Look at
what farmers do during the rainy season. The
crop is abundant when there is good rain. It is not that it will
say after the rains, that is, after the
rains are over. It is not like this now. You
need shares right now. It is the rainy season, right now, you have time to
sow seeds. At this time, we will do half a minute
when this rail breaks out, that is, the
line will give day. Then it is difficult to get into this category.
Then which one  This resistance of Rangers will become
support, meaning it will
come down and then go back, it will
not come down, you have to keep this thing in mind, so
friends, what do you have to do in this city, you have to keep
tweeting like this every month and AB no
friends, I want to give you a disclaimer
that I have holdings in this sector,
I am doing SIP on it every month, so
you don't have to think that I am doing it, so what you have to do is you have to use your
brain a little, you have to
decide a little, after that you can go,
but I guarantee you that
whatever stock I tell you here, it is fundamentally strong, I do
not talk about it as per the floating trend, there is no discount, well, no
one talks about it, which you can use later, you can
definitely test it, but
you also have to do a little bit with your dreams and
friends, a combination, you mean
research, there should be a little bit from your side,
you should keep this
thing in mind, friends, you will find that
you will create a good will, so I
hope you liked it, if you liked it then
like and share it, if you liked more
videos then like and share  I have
subscribed to the channel, if you haven't already, please
subscribe, friends. See you in the
next video. Some next wrong
cricketer will be about this and together we will make
a great family of Belt Krishna. See you in the next
video, friends. And
how it is raining, Jai Hind, Jai Bharat.